ZZ Top: 美国摇滚三人组 其中两人留着长胡子
您的账单 ZZ先生和Top先生
Here's your check, Mr. ZZ and Mr. Top.
您是要个打包盒
Would you like a to-go box,
还是打算把剩下的三明治
or are you just gonna put it in your beard
直接塞胡子里带走?
with the rest of your sandwich?
我们参加了个"留胡子"大赛
We're in a beard-growing contest.
是全国性的
They happen all over the country.
这可是件大事
It's a pretty big deal.
头等奖是什么?
What's first prize?
送女友的眼罩?
Blindfold for your girlfriends?
我瞎说的 一看就知道你们是光棍
I'm kidding, I know you don't have girlfriends.
事实上 像这样的发艺
Actually, this level of hair-art
需要数个月的辛苦付出
takes months of hard work and commitment.
鸭子王朝: 美国真人秀节目 主角大多留着长胡子
嘎嘎 "鸭子王朝"
Well, quack, quack, Duck Dynasty.
还没我左侧的腋毛长呢
My left armpit could beat you both.
我代表所有女人奉劝你们一句
Let me tell you something on behalf of women everywhere.
我们 很不 喜欢 胡子
We. Don't. Like. Beards.
又作蓄须随从 即陪伴已婚男子与女友约会 用以掩人耳目的人
Caroline? 胡子?
Caroline? Beards?
我向来不愿给人当
I never liked being one.
姐妹们 要是那男的叫Trace 就趁早闪人
Ladies, if his name is Trace, get the hell out of there.
看到了吧? 赶紧剃了 衰货们
See? So, shave losers.
就连没下巴或多个下巴
If you're chinless or chin-plentiful,
都比你们现在的模样强
it's better than what you've got going on.
给您的建议 待会给小费也请大方点
There's your tip, be generous with mine.
你居然骂了人还指望人家
You actually insult people and then expect them
白白送你钱?
to give you money?
你我不就是这样嘛
That's how it works with you and me.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
破产姐妹花 第四季第12集
协调: 。沫   时间轴: Morning
翻译: 奥利奥 Morning Astral
校对: 酱油影
谢谢惠顾
Thanks.
咱们新出的纸杯蛋糕T恤真是抢手
Everyone's loving our new cupcake T-shirts.
光过去四个小时就卖了四件
I've sold four in the last hour.
再卖三件就买得起咱们相中的毛巾了
Three more and we can afford that towel we've had our eye on.
这些T恤大卖
These T-shirts keep selling.
意味着财源滚滚
That means more money.
越是有钱 越是有本事
Mo' means mo' success.
"有本事"?
Mo' Success?
我应该和他表弟"没本事"约过会
I think I dated his cousin, Les.
嘿 各位亲
Hey, everybody.
我能先喘口气吗?
Mind if I stop for a breather?
我可是"忙新娘"忙坏了
I've been "briding" my ass off.
Sophie 这些都是你买的新婚杂志吗?
Sophie, are those all your bridal magazines?
这里才一半
That's only half.
快过来 Oleg!
Come on, Oleg!
听着 要是这些都嫌重 你打算怎么
Look, if those are too heavy, how are you going to be able
把喜驴一路推过走道?
to push the wedding donkey down the aisle?
喜驴?
Wedding donkey?
我对这场婚礼的期待值刚刚爆表了
My excitement level for this wedding just skyrocketed.
别担心 Sophie
Relax, Sophie.
要是我只会做一件事 那就是怎么推屁股
If I know how to do anything, it's how to move an ass.
这话不假
That's true. Yeah.
哇 你手上的杂志数量比阿曼达・拜恩斯的心理问题还多
Wow, you're carrying more heavy issues than Amanda Bynes.
看看这些 "佳丽新娘"
Look at all these. Beautiful Bride,
"时尚新娘" "都市新娘"?
Modern Bride, City Bride?
你真得需要"非裔新娘"吗?
And do you really need African American Bride?
我这不还没完全放弃玉米辫嘛
Well, I haven't ruled out cornrows.
玉米辫配喜驴?
Cornrows and a donkey?
请告诉是真的
RSVP yes.
对了
Oh, yeah.
这妞性感
This one's hot.
待我留着回头欣赏
Save that one for later.
我差点忘了我是待婚之人
Oh, I forgot I'm getting married.
留着她
Keep her.
我周二可能要请个假
I might need a Tuesday off.
Sophie 为什么不找你的伴娘帮忙?
Sophie, why don't you get some help from your Maid of Honor?
我要杀了你
I will kill you.
或者雇个婚礼策划人?
Or a wedding planner?
想起来了 Sophie 我表妹Svetlana就是策划婚礼的
Oh, Sophie, my cousin, Svetlana, is a wedding planner.
那好 她最好在行
Okay, but she better be good.
因为我的大婚之日要求万无一失
Because I want everything to be perfect on my big day.
我俩的大婚之日
Our big day.
是 行
Yeah. Sure.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
他们就要结婚了 而我的喜驴
They're getting married and I don't have a wedding donkey
却不着天际
anywhere on my horizon.
天啊 你们卖这款T恤?
OMG, you sell these T-shirts?
我刚买了件
I just bought one.
我是刚卖完你衣服 就忘了这事吗?
Did I just sell you that shirt and already forgot?
早知道那瓶九分钱的除臭剂
I knew that nine-cent deodorant
会给我大脑创伤的
was going to give me brain lesions.
标签上的确贴了张大脑图
Well, the label did have a picture of a brain
还标明"不带甲酮"
with "No Bueno" written on it.
不 我是在曼哈顿的一家店买的
No, I bought it at a store in Manhattan
就在东九道和百老汇那
on East Ninth and Broadway.
我是因为强迫症才知道的 它离街角
I know because I'm OCD and it was 67 steps
一共隔了67步和14条人行道
and 14 sidewalk cracks from the corner.
Max 有人在卖我们的衣服
Max, someone else is selling our shirts.
我知道
I know.
我们被别人坑了
We're getting hosed by some other hoes.
他们竟敢抄袭我们的衣服
I can't believe they stole our shirt.
我们唯一受顾客青睐的产品
The one thing we made that people actually wanted to buy.
跟"我的空间"一个遭遇
I feel like MySpace.
我好久没对一个展柜如此气愤了
I haven't seen anything this upsetting in a window
上一次还是我不小心瞥见镜中
since that time I accidentally caught a reflection
自己穿服务生制服的样子
of myself in my waitress uniform.
我们得找人说理
We need to talk to someone
评评这些被抬高价钱的衣服
about those damn shirts you jacked.
我们来闹事的
We about to rumble.
她的意思是 我们想找人谈谈
What she means is, we wish to speak to someone
展柜里那些可爱的纸杯蛋糕T恤
about the adorable cupcake T-shirts in the window.
不然就要闹事
Or, we will be about to rumble.
我在这不过是打点零工
I'm just working here till I get my PhD
就等着考上西方文明社会经济学博士
in the Eco-Social Dynamics of Western Civilization.
也就是说 等一辈子?
So, forever?
这些T恤是我们设计的
Those T-shirts are our design
我们想弄清为什么这里有卖
and we need to know why they're here
以及是谁剽窃的
and who knocked them off.
是本店老板娘的孙女
It's the granddaughter of the woman who owns this shop.
她算个折腾精 而且她要进来了
She's kind of a monster and she's walking in right now.
嗨 Kemberly和Ashlin
Hi, Kemberly and Ashlin.
这两位女士对你的T恤很感兴趣
These ladies are interested in your T-shirts.
挺可爱的吧?
Aren't they cute?
可爱死了
So cute.
是 可爱得不得了
Yeah, super cute.
我们设计的
We designed them.
对 我们设计的
Yeah, we designed them.
什么?
What?
对 什么?
Yeah, what?
Ashlin和Kimberly 对吧?
Ashlin and Kimberly, is it?
是Kemberly 带字母E的
It's Kemberly, with an "E""
我自己改的名 因为我很独特
I changed it myself 'cause I'm original.
对 她是独特的
Yeah, she's an original.
你知道什么不算独特(原创)吗?
You know what's not original?
这些衣服 你们抄袭我们的
Those shirts. You stole them from us.
我们没剽窃你的创意
We did not steal your idea.
对 我们没剽窃你的创意
Yeah, we did not steal your idea.
我们抄袭的是布鲁克林一家破纸杯蛋糕店
We copied it from this lame cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
等等...
Wait a minute...
我们就在布鲁克林开了一家纸杯蛋糕店
we have a lame cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
Ashlin 你太多嘴
Ashlin, you talk too much.
大家就是这么知道我做了胃束带手术的
This is why everyone knows about my lap-band.
我觉得他们之所以知道 是因为你短短一个春假间
I think they know about it because you lost 200 pounds
瘦了200镑
over Spring break.
真不敢相信她过去比现在还可恶两倍
It's hard to believe she was once twice this obnoxious.
若不停售我们的T恤
If you don't stop selling our T-shirts,
就只能让我们的律师接管了
we're gonna have to get our lawyer involved.
对 让我们的律师接管
Yeah, we're gonna have to get our lawyer involved.
然后他会杀了你的
And he's gonna kill you.
我不知道什么是律师
I don't know what lawyers do.
我们绝不是为了私利而为
We're totally not doing this for us.
我们很有钱的
We're rich.
对 我们很有钱
Yeah, we're rich.
每卖出一件衣服 就有一部分善款捐给慈善组织
A percentage of every shirt that we sell goes to charity.
对 捐给慈善组织
Yeah, it goes to charity.
我们就是需要被捐助的人
We are the charity that it needs to go to.
你们又老又缺钱
You're old and desperate for money.
我很能理解
And I totally get it.
我姑姑也是纽约的"绝望主妇"之一
My aunt's one of the Real Housewives of New York.
但是 抱歉
But, sorry.
是缺一条腿的那个
It's the one without the leg.
刚刚在这里发生了什么?
What just happened here?
那姑娘刚刚说你老
That girl just called you old.
Earl 我想我最近一段时间不会给你买
Earl, I don't think I'm going to be buying you that pinky ring
你要的尾戒
you wanted any time soon.
不急 Max 你有的是时间
No rush, Max, you got plenty of time.
在我入土之前 我还有六七个月的时间
I got like, six or seven months before I turn to dust.
这是因为我们的衬衫
It's 'cause our T-shirts got ripped off
被几个曼哈顿的预科学校的妹子给剽窃了
by a couple of prep school girls in Manhattan.
就像一部80年代的劣质电影
It's like a bad 80's movie.
我不知道该去跟詹姆斯・斯派德约会
I don't know whether to date James Spader
还是去教镇上的人跳舞
or teach this town how to dance.
这太不公平了
This is so unfair.
那些姑娘不能就这么偷我们的东西
Those girls can't just steal from us.
这又不是7-11便利店
This isn't 7-Eleven.
Max 我没想到你居然这么天真
Max, I can't believe your naivete?
这跟我飞溅的口水有什么关系?
What does my body spray have to do with anything?
听着 我们没理由对那俩姑娘
Look, there is no reason to be so upset
感到不爽
about those two girls.
他们不会影响我们的生意
They're not going to affect our business.
而且 他们不得不自我煎熬
Plus, they have to live with themselves.
因果报应向来很准
And karma is a bitch.
我是说 我曾经乱丢垃圾 再看我遭了什么报应
I mean, I littered once and look what happened to me.
嘿 各位亲
Hey, everybody.
婚礼的废品把我弄疯了
I'm up to my nuts in bridal junk.
她来了
There she is.
我一生的挚爱
The love of my life.
她是我勃起时要的阴道
The yin to my yang.
也是我阳痿时的性奋剂
The zing to my wang.
把你的金句留到宣誓再说
Save that gold for the vows.
我叫Svetlana 是Oleg的表姐妹
I am Svetlana, Oleg's cousin.
亲爱的 还能更糟点
Well, darling, it could be worse.
你可以当他的亲姐妹
You could be his sister.
嗨 Svetty!
Svetty!
你一定就是Sophie
And you must be Sophie.
是
Yeah.
不
No.
她还什么都没说呢
But you haven't even heard any ideas.
Caroline啊
Caroline.
Sophie 你为什么叫我的名字?
Sophie, why did you just say my name?
哦 这是我和Oleg的暗号
Oh, it's Oleg's and my safe word.
意思是"不"
Yeah. It means no.
这是我们一致同意不会在做爱过程中说的话
It's the one word we both agreed we would never say during sex.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
因为预定婚礼策划附赠汽车换油保养一次哦
Because I give free oil change with every wedding.
Caroline啊
Caroline.
好吧 我要坐我的位置
All right, well, I'll be in my booth.
婚礼策划人和同名电影"婚礼策划人"
You know, this wedding planner thing is as crappy as the movie
一样垃圾
of the same name.
姑娘们 我忘了告诉你们
Girls, I forgot to tell you,
今天来的一个男人拿了封信给你们
a man came by today with this letter for you.
这让我想起自己还是年轻能干的快递员的时候
This reminds me of when I was a young, hot-shot courier.
我以前也是年轻能干的快递员
I was a young, hot-shot courier once, too.
我曾经踩着三轮车 给正在上班的我妈送毒品
I used to deliver drugs to my mother at work on my tricycle.
天啊 Max 你不会相信的
Oh, my God, Max, you're not gonna believe this,
但那俩姑娘已经申请了停止不正当竞争的命令
but those two girls have issued a Cease and Desist order.
那俩贱人
Those bitches.
那是什么?
What's that?
她们要求我们必须停止出售我们的衬衫
They're saying we have to stop selling our T-shirts.
这正是我告诉他们 我们要做的事
That's what I told them we were going to do.
他们连这个想法都抄袭了
They even copied this idea.
我们需要一个律师
We need to get a lawyer.
怎么请? 我们连iTunes上的"法律与秩序"(美剧)都买不起
How? We can't even afford Law & Order on iTunes.
嘿 你觉得我们请得起地铁广告牌上的
Hey, do you think we could afford that lawyer
律师吗?
on the subway billboards?
一手拿着锤子一手拿着只鸡的那个?
The one who has a gavel in one hand and a chicken in the other?
我想他只会导致交通事故
I think he just does acidentes.
这是什么情况啊?
What is going on here?
菜在窗口晾着
There's food waiting in the window,
杂志四处散着
periodicals strewn about.
某人大姨夫又来了
Someone's on his periodical.
Han 我们刚刚被人摆了一道
Han, we just got served.
至少餐厅里还有人被招待
At least someone in the diner has.
你们很幸运 你们的老板这么冷静
You're lucky your boss is so chill.
你当然冷了 你是"波普先生的企鹅"中的一只
Of course you're chill, you're one of Mr. Popper's penguins.
这么着怎么样?
How about this?
如果你同意假扮我们的律师
We'll do the jobs you already pay us for
我们就会完成你付了工钱的工作
if you agree to pretend to be our lawyer.
你有西装 对吧?
You have a suit, right?
我为什么要假扮律师?
Why would I pretend to be a lawyer?
你们连假扮服务员都不会
You can't even pretend to be waitresses.
不管怎样 没人会相信Han是我们的律师
No one's gonna believe Han's our lawyer, anyway.
他无法通过律师资格考试 他连眼睛都不够吧台高
He can't pass the bar, he can barely see over one.
够了! 我受够你们俩和你们那套不工作的理论了
That's it! I've had it with you two and your non-work ethic.
这里是为顾客服务的
And this area is for customers.
我要这些东西出去!
I want these out of here!
嗷!
Ow!
完了
Uh-oh.
Max吗?
Max?
只要这样做你能忘了我砸你这件事
I suppose I could dig up a suit if that could, somehow,
我想我会想办法翻出套西装来
make this boss striking his employee thing go away.
Max 这些姑娘当然会去Dalby Hall
Max, of course these girls go to Dalby Hall,
我的所有敌人都去了
all my archenemies did.
但是我猜Lady Gaga最后会赢
I guess Lady Gaga won in the end, though.
另一则新闻 我有点喜欢这个眼罩
In other news, I kind of like this eye-patch.
我知道你喜欢 你刚刚一直在地铁里
I know you do, you were pretending to be
假扮海盗女王
the pirate queen of the subway.
没人敢跟我们撕逼
Well, no one arrrrrgued with us.
眼科医生说你得带着它多长时间?
How long did the eye doctor say you have to keep it on?
我说的眼科医生是我们送了免费点心给他的
And by eye doctor, I mean that first-year med student
那个一年级医学生
we gave the free dessert to.
难过的日子只有一只眼能看见
A few days, which is a bummer, 'cause only seeing half
也算是种幸福
of how sad we are is kind of a blessing.
我们要怎么找到她们?
How are we gonna find them?
循着我们没落的衬衫生意的气息吗?
Follow the scent of our decaying T-shirts business?
根据Instagram 她们在自助餐厅 看见没?
According to Instagram, they're in the cafeteria, see?
Ashlin刚刚发了一张迷你披萨的照片
Ashlin just posted a pic of a mini-pizza.
#披萨生活
#thatpizzalife
这里有迷你披萨?
They have mini-pizzas here?
我的高中连熟食都没有
My high school didn't even have heat.
抱歉我迟到了 我得去男士服装大卖场
Sorry I'm late. I had to pick up a suit
买套西装
at the Men's Warehouse.
你说的是"不完全是男士"服装大卖场吗?
Don't you mean the Not Quite A Man's Warehouse?
Han 我喜欢你的律师服 很逼真啊
Han, I love your lawyer costume. So authentic.
唯一缺少的就是你的灵魂
Only thing missing is the hole where your soul should be.
我一直都说 如果你要做某件事...
Well, as I always say, if you're going to do something...
用你的左手做 这样就会觉得是别人做的?
Do it with your left hand so it will feel like someone else?
不是 如果你要做某件事 就好好做
No, if you're going to do something, do it right.
去年万圣节 我扮演的是"绿巨人"广告里的豌豆芽
Last Halloween, I went as Sprout from the Green Giant commercial
我还把豌豆荚放在我的鸡鸡上
and I even put pea pods over my pee-pee.
你们笑了 但我赢了五百美元
You laugh, but I won $500.
好了 我写了份自己的停止不正当竞争的命令
Okay, I created my own Cease and Desist order.
你从哪儿来的这个?
Where did you get this?
和Max打印那份假的
Same place Max printed out that fake,
"我没有疱疹"的医生证明是同一个地方
"I don't have herpe" doctor certificate.
还生效了
It works.
这是你的名片
And here's your business card.
哪儿? 在哪儿?
Where? Where is it?
我看不见
I can't see.
给你 Han 我希望你是个比Max更好的演员
Here. And Han, I hope you're a better actor than Max.
巨石强森(摔角选手)是个比Max更好的演员
Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson is a better actor than Max.
鲁诉先生?
Mr. Lu Su?
这就是你想出来的?
That's what you came up with?
鲁诉先生?
Mr. Lu Su?
你是个律师 所以"诉"这个字完全符合
Well, you're a lawyer, so the "Su" part is totally on point.
但是鲁诉?
But Lu Su?
从来没有亚洲人叫这个名字的
No Asian was ever named that.
这个星球上也许没有
Maybe not in this galaxy,
但我可以提醒你有个苏鲁先生(星际迷航)
but might I remind you of a Mr. Sulu.
没错 我把它重组了 天才啊!
Oh, yeah. I mixed it up. Genius!
Han 你不必用这些名片
Han, you don't have to use the cards.
我会好好利用的
I can make it work.
两年前的万圣节 我扮演的是伊沃克人(星球大战)
Two Halloweens ago, I was an Ewok
然后把橙色的浴巾变成了穆斯林的头巾
and turned an orange bath-towel into a turban.
二等奖 奖金250美元
Second place. $250.
明年万圣节的时候 你就能穿着那个
And next Halloween, you can wear that
扮成蕾丝边了
and goes as a lesbian minister.
好吧 我们这么办 我们进去
Okay, so the plan is, we go in there
和我们的律师一起 冷静地和她们对质
and calmly confront them with our attorney.
我来负责说话
I'll do the talking.
Han 你站着 装作你很聪明就可以了
Han, you stand there and try to look smart.
啊 我是个亚洲人 所以这事已经搞定了
Ah. I'm already Asian. So, done.
哇 这让我想起了过去
Wow, this brings me back.
我曾和校园风云人物 辩论队
I had a seat at the popular table, the Debate Team table,
学生会的人
the Student Council table,
还有一起等结婚的人坐过一桌
and the Waiting For Marriage table.
但是那一桌后来就散了
But that table kind of fell apart
因为除了我以外 所有人都怀孕了
when everybody got pregnant but me.
我和一个酒鬼在学校的停车场里一起吃饭
I ate in the school parking lot with a wino.
他对我非常好 我还以为他可能是我爸呢
He was so nice to me, I thought he might be my dad.
但他一直没有对我动手动脚
But then he never made a move on me,
所以看来他不是
so I guess he wasn't.
各位注意一下
Attention everyone, attention.
是啊 各位注意一下
Yeah, attention everyone, attention.
Ashilin和我今天来卖我们的T恤衫
Ashlin and I are here today to sell our T-shirts
并告诉你们 欺负人是件很不好的事
and to talk about bullying and how it's not cool.
太不好了
It's so not cool.
我在说话呢 Ash
I was talking, Ash.
是啊 她在说话呢
Yeah, she was talking.
她们是为校园欺凌筹钱?
Their charity is bullying?
这就好像坎耶・维斯特为低调而筹钱一样
That's like Kanye West trying to raise money for laying low.
每买一件我们的超可爱T恤
A $3 donation will be made to our anti-bullying fund
就会给我们的反校园欺凌基金捐款3美元
with each purchase of one of our super, super cute tees.
超级 超级可爱的T恤
Super, super cute tees.
这是我的超可爱T恤!
My super cute tee!
那是我这辈子最好的主意
Best idea I ever had.
还有就是一个下巴带
Right up there with the bong with a chin strap
可以让你把手空出来换台
so you could be hands-free to change the channel.
赶紧买一件T恤吧 我们马上回来
So buy a shirt right now and then we'll be back later
继续我们的反校园欺凌演讲
for the rest of the anti-bully talk.
是啊 你们要是不买
Yeah, buy them or my dad won't pay
我爸爸今年就不给大家买长曲棍球装备了
for the lacrosse equipment this year.
我们走 他们在利用我们赚大钱
Let's go. They are making a fortune on us.
如果我要被人搞 那最好也是21岁以上的人
And if I'm gonna get screwed, it better be by someone over 21.
是啊 这好像只需要两杯酒就可以搞定了
Yeah, that sounds like a job with a two drink minimum.
Han 别把这事搞砸了 否则就让你把这眼镜吃了
Han, don't mess this up or you'll be eating those glasses.
你想要反校园欺凌的小册子吗?
Might I interest you in an anti-bullying pamphlet?
你想坐在我的手指上吗?
Might I interest you in a seat on my finger?
嘿 你们两个怎么进来的?
Hey, how did you two get in here?
学校花钱请了门卫 不放流浪汉进来呢
The school pays guards out front to keep out the homeless.
是啊 真好笑
Yeah, well, jokes on you.
因为他们刚刚就直接让我们走进来了
'Cause they just let us walk in.
你们好啊 小姑娘 你们可以停止
Hello, girls. You can "Cease and Desis"
售卖我们的T恤了
selling our T-shirts as of now.
这是我们的律师 他叫...
This is our attorney, Mr....
鲁诉先生
Lu Su.
他手里拿着我们的禁止令
And he is holding our Cease and Desist
来回应你们的禁止令
to counter your Cease and Desist.
好吧 首先 你们的律师看上去像个
Okay, well, first, your lawyer looks like a teacher
迪士尼里的老师
on a Disney show.
这不好吗?
Is that a bad thing?
如果你们还想说什么的话
And if you have anything further to say,
你们可以去找我的律师 也就是她爸爸
you can take it up with my lawyer. Her dad.
他真的很厉害
And he's real good.
他用了技术手段帮一个承认自己杀了他全家的
He got that CEO guy who admitted he killed his whole family
首席执行官脱了罪
out on a technicality.
我忘了女孩们能有多恶毒了
I forgot how mean girls can be.
这怎么会? 我可是你室友啊
How? I'm your roommate.
谢谢你 Kemberly 谢谢 Ashilin
Thank you, Kemberly. Thank you, Ashlin.
能帮帮忙吗
A little help.
姑娘们 你们好 你们看上去人挺好的
Hello, girls, you all look very nice.
他在干什么?
What is he doing?
希望他干得漂亮点 然后就能吸引到人给来个头条
Hopefully a tight ten and then he'll bring up the headliner.
也许看着我 穿着这么帅气的西装
This may be hard to believe, looking at me
会很难相信
in this totally awesome suit,
我比较了解被欺负的感受
but I know a little something about being bullied.
当我还是小孩的时候...
As a little child...
还是一个稍微大一点的成人
And as a slightly bigger adult.
你怎么这样? 他在进行校园欺凌演讲 你还要欺负他?
Seriously? In the middle of his bullying speech, you're bullying?
我自己都有点吃惊
Kind of surprised even myself.
有人欺负我
I have someone who bullies me.
好吧 趁来得及我们先出去
Okay, let's get out of here while I can.
这不仅仅是打我和叫外号
It's not just the hitting and the name-calling.
虽然 说实话 这很令人沮丧
Although, not gonna lie, that's a real bummer.
但你们看 姑娘们 被欺负的坏处在于
You see, girls, the bad thing about being bullied
你每一次被欺负 生命的一小部分
is that every time it happens, it steals a little piece
就会被偷走
of who you are.
反复多次之后 一点一点的
And then, if it happens enough, little by little,
你就会变得不如你能成为的那种人
you become just a little less of who you were meant to be.
而这很不好
And that's not cool.
这里的两个女孩虽然还没意识到 但我相信
And these two girls up here, without knowing it, I'm sure,
她们在偷走Max和Caroline的创意时
stole a little piece of Max and Caroline.
也偷走了她们生命中的一小部分东西
when they stole their little idea.
而那也很不好
And that's so not cool.
是啊 那太不好了
Yeah, that's so not cool.
Max 还有Caroline 我们不会再做这些衬衫了
Max, Caroline, we'll stop making the shirts.
Ash 我可没这么说过
Ash, I never said that.
不 Kemberly 我说了
Ah, no, Kemberly. I did.
而且我更喜欢接受胃束带手术之前的你
And I liked you more before the lap-band.
当时你的名字还是带I的Kimberly
When you were still Kimberly with an "I."
Max 刚刚Han是不是救了我们?
Max, did Han just save us?
我没在听 我忙着把小披萨
I wasn't listening, I was putting mini-pizzas
偷装进口袋呢
in my pocket.
姑娘们 你们四十分钟之前就该开始上班了
Girls, your shift started 40 minutes ago.
你们那么早来干什么?
What are you doing here so early?
Earl 我们有好消息 现在我们是
Earl, good news. We are now the sole owners
纸杯蛋糕T恤的唯一销售商了
of all those cupcake T-shirts.
我们也没别的东西了
And, literally, nothing else.
也许我可以租一只鹦鹉 然后去
Maybe I could rent a parrot and pick up some shifts
梅因餐馆上几天班
at Long John Silver's.
嘿 姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我马上就要见一个新的婚礼策划了
I'm about to meet another wedding planner.
这个人会很棒的!
And this one's gonna be good!
他是同性恋
He's gay.
Sophie Kuchenski吗?
Sophie Kuchenski?
是啊 天啊!
Yes, God!
我刚走进这里 我就对自己说
From the second I walked in here, I said to myself,
"那肯定是她" 我看得出来
"That has to be her." And I can see it.
我们要一起创造魔法了
We're going to make magic together.
是啊 同性恋怎么说不?
Yeah, what's gay for no?
好吧
Okay.
哇 我感觉我们刚刚经历了一场"同卷风"
Wow, I think we just survived a "Torgaydo""
我现在在纽约去哪里再找一个同性恋
Where am I gonna find another gay wedding planner
婚礼策划啊?
in New York now?
在Crate & Barrel家装店发一次脾气
Just throw a tantrum in a Crate & Barrel,
就会有五个跑着过来了
and five of them will come running.
嘿 今天法律工作干得不错
Hey, nice legal work today.
你都能上儿童法庭了
You should be on the Little People's Court.
是啊 从现在开始 我要叫你Han大律师了
Yeah, from now on, I'm calling you "Hanny Cochran""
好吧 下次你们想感谢我
Okay. Next time you want to thank me,
就给我送一份爱蒂宝甜点吧
just send me an Edible Arrangement.
我都不知道暗示你们多少次了
I don't know many times I have to drop that hint.
但那就好像是个两英寸的暗示了
But that's just, like, a two-inch drop.
对不起 我忍不住
Sorry. I can't help myself.
但我还是想问问看 因为我知道我就是
But I'm going to try because I know I was the bully
你在那个演讲里说的那个欺负你的人
you were talking about in that speech.
什么? 我说的是我那栋大楼的门房
What? I was talking about the doorwoman in my building.
我每次要拿邮件
I have to submit to a purple-nurple
都得被揪奶头
just to get my mail.
你还有别的女人?
There's another woman?
Max 我觉得Han有个二房
Max, I think Han has a side bully.
好吧 那看来我得更努力了
Well, I'll just have to try harder.
因为如果有人要揪你的奶头
Because if anyone is gonna mercilessly nurple you
那也得是我
into an early grave, it's got to be me.
我也想这样 Max
I'd like to think so, Max.
你还想坐车头朝前的车呢
You'd also like to ride in a car facing forwards.
又是老样子
Back to normal.